stahls.com 2018-12-17

# Privacy Policy | Stahls'

We (“Company”) welcome you to a website (“Site”) associated with Stahls’ Inc. d/b/a GroupeSTAHL, a leading international manufacturer, distributor and direct supplier in the field of custom textile printing. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, “Company” shall have the same meaning as in the “Terms and Conditions” of this Site. 

The Company respects the privacy of our users and has created this Privacy Policy to describe our policy about the collection, use, security and disclosure of information we obtain from users of the Site. We encourage you to take time to read and understand this Privacy Policy, and to contact us if you have any questions or concerns regarding this Privacy Policy. This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of the “Terms and Conditions” for this Site. By using the Site, you consent to our collection, use and disclosure of your information, including personally identifiable information, as described in this Policy. 

##  Information Collected by the Company 

_Automatically Collected Information_  
We may automatically receive and store certain types of non-personally identifiable information, including information about your use of our Site, your interactions with other users on the Site, the type of web browser you are using, the website that led you to our Site, the website you go to after leaving our Site, the pages you view on our Site, the dates and times you access our Site, and information about any orders you place, such as your order identification number, items ordered and the cost of your order. We may collect Site visitation statistical information through cookies, tools such as Google Analytics, and other technology, to speed navigation of the Site by allowing the Site to recognize each user and his or her access privileges and to track the user’s usage of the Site. 

_Log Files_  
The Site server automatically recognizes the Internet Uniform Resource Locator (“URL”) from which you access the Site. We may also log your Internet protocol ("IP") address, which may be helpful, for example, for system administration and troubleshooting purposes. (An IP address indicates the location of your computer on the Internet.) 

_Information Collected from Other Sources_  
If you access the Site through a third-party social media account (such as OpenID, Google+, Facebook. LinkedIn, Twitter), we may access information about you from that third-party source, including your user ID for the third-party source and certain information from your profile for that third-party source. The Site may combine information that we collect with information from all third-party sources. 

##  How The Company Uses and Discloses the Information it Collects 

We use and may disclose your information to our employees, contractors and other third parties to facilitate the services you request, to create accounts and allow use of services and ordering of products on the Site. We use your information to resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems and enforce our Terms and Conditions. We may use personally identifiable information about you to improve our marketing and promotional efforts, to analyze Site usage, improve our content and product offerings, and customize the Site's content, layout and services. 

The Company may use your information to contact you and deliver information to you that, in some cases, is targeted to your interests and relevant to your use of the Site. In addition to sending you promotional emails about our services, from time to time, we may send you promotional emails about our affiliates, subsidiaries or other third parties. 

Without limitation to the foregoing, We may modify your personally identifiable information such that it is not identifiable as yours, and we may store, analyze, manipulate, aggregate, display, disclose, distribute, retain and otherwise use such unidentifiable information without restriction. 

The Company will not sell or rent personally identifiable information about you to a third party. 

We may use Google AdSense, Google AdMob and other third-party advertising companies to serve advertising when you visit the Site. We may use web analytics tools, such as Google Analytics, to analyze your use of the Services. These third-party advertising companies may use information about your use of the Services in order to provide advertisements for goods and services that are targeted to you. 

In some case it is possible to opt-out from personally targeted advertising. 

  * With Google you can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Preferences page at: <https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/authenticated>
  * Another example is the DoubleClick opt-out page at: [https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/anonymous?sig=ACi0TCj_XDmT8bSGTOqn3mSeIfTYdyz6GkqmR9oUNwOCKND_h9kxXvQkOJJlKL5fEwscSpV6L1dM8dAIJYRj8SEec2S1oAgoOCFx06hOHTyTNGIKe0Fxf30&hl=en#display_optout](https://www.google.com/settings/u/0/ads/anonymous?sig=ACi0TCj_XDmT8bSGTOqn3mSeIfTYdyz6GkqmR9oUNwOCKND_h9kxXvQkOJJlKL5fEwscSpV6L1dM8dAIJYRj8SEec2S1oAgoOCFx06hOHTyTNGIKe0Fxf30&hl=en#display_optout)
  * A further example is the Network Advertising Initiative Opt-Out page at: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/choices/>

We cannot ensure that all of your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. The Company may disclose any information about you if required by law or under the compulsion of legal process, or in connection with any licensing, sale, merger, transfer or other disposition associated with all or a portion of its business. We may also disclose information about you if, in our sole discretion, we believe such disclosure is necessary or appropriate in connection with an investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, or other activity that is illegal or may expose us or you to legal consequences. 

## Security

No computer system or information can ever be fully protected against every possible hazard. In order to help protect your information and the information and data contained on our Site, The Company employs reasonable and appropriate technical, physical and administrative security measures. Communications with our Site are encrypted through Secured Socket Layer (“SSL”) connections. We also follow industry-accepted security procedures such as encrypted administrative communication, restricted access to underlying machines, and firewalls at network access points. 

**THE COMPANY CANNOT GUARANTEE SECURITY. THE COMPANY ASSUMES NO RESPONSIBILITY OR LIABILITY FOR DISCLOSURE OF YOUR PERSONALLY IDENTIFIABLE INFORMATION THAT OCCURS BY NEGLIGENCE OF THE COMPANY, ERRORS IN TRANSMISSION, UNAUTHORIZED OR ILLEGAL ACCESS, OR ANY OTHER VEHICLE FOR DISCLOSURE.

THE SITE CONTAINS LINKS TO OTHER WEBSITES. THE COMPANY IS NOT RESPONSIBLE FOR THE CONTENT, TERMS OF USE, OR PRIVACY POLICIES ON ANY THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES, OR PRIVACY PRACTICES BY ANY THIRD PARTIES.

**

Company’s obligations under this Privacy Policy do not apply to any information or data that: (a) is not identifiable as yours; (b) is or becomes entirely in the public domain with a breach of this Privacy Policy by Company; (c) was known to Company prior to its access to the information or data through this Site; (d) received lawfully from a third party through no breach of any obligation of confidentiality owed to you; and/or (e) created by Company independently of its access to or use of your personally identifiable information. 

## Children Under Thirteen

The Company does not knowingly accept personal information from anyone under the age of 13. By using the Site and/or providing personal information, you represent and warrant that you are over the age of 13. 

## Updating Your Information/Opting Out

You may contact us at [info@stahls.com](mailto:info@stahls.com) at any time to update and/or correct your information, to opt-out of receiving future communications from us or to deactivate your account. Additionally, you may automatically review and change the information you submit to the Company by logging into the Site and updating your account information yourself. When the Company receives a request to deactivate or cancel your account, we will take commercially reasonable efforts to remove your personally identifiable information from our databases, but we cannot guarantee that your information will be completely deleted due to the necessity of redundancy inherent in the electronic storage and management of data. We also may retain copies of your personally identifiable information as required by our record retention policies. When you deactivate your account, your member profile will be deactivated, but your public comments may remain on the Site. The Company has no responsibility to take down or remove any of your public activities or submissions.

## Changes to Our Privacy Policy

The Company may amend this Privacy Policy from time to time by posting the amended terms on this Site. You are responsible for regularly reviewing this Privacy Policy and all such amended terms. By viewing, using or accessing the Site after any amended terms have been posted, you consent to the Privacy Policy and Terms and Conditions of the Site then in effect.

## Contact Information

If you have any questions, comments, complaints or concerns about this Privacy Policy or your privacy, contact us at [Legal@stahls.com](mailto:legal@stahls.com).
